# Vekariya Kishan Ramanikbhai

204- Radha swami Apartment - A, Puna Gaam Road, Surat. Gujarat - india 394110. 9586382258 | vekariyakishan.143@gmail.com



## Objective

A good position in the organisation which provides the opportunity to make a strong contribution towards the organizational goals through continued development of professional skills. Would be interested in learning the organisational skills and tactics under the guidance of the Industry giants with great precision and expertise.

### **Experience**

#### Management

01/07/2020 -Shreeji overseas

**C. D. U** 2018 - 2020 Adani port

#### Team leader

2014 - 2017 Flipkart

#### Sales executive

2013 - 2014 Sun visions technology IT Sale's executive

# Education

Ladoution			
Course / Degree	School / University	Grade / Score	Year
B.Com	Sourashtra University	56	2012
Hardware Networking	C++, Os	А	2009

## Skills

1:- I.T SKILLS ■ Opreting Systems. ■ Ms Excel. ■ Data Entry. ■ Mailing. 2:- BUSINESS ORINTEAD RESPONSIBILITY. ■ Team Building ■ Time Management work ■ Customer Satisfaction Service. ■ Quality Control. ■ Purchasing & Sales R/m. ■ Dispatching ■ Inbound-Outbound ■ Prepare Finals Report.

# Languages

Hindi

Gujarati

Marwadi			
Marathi			
English			
Personal Details			
Date of Birth	19/02/1992		
Marital Status	Married		
Religion	Hinduism		
Hometown	Junagadh		

## Reference

Mahendra Gokhruji.. - " Shreeji Overseas. (Mines&Minarals). Bhilwara, Rajasthan "
Owner
Concept.shreeji@gmail.com
9829046223